{
  "1" : [
    {
      "question": "What is sushi traditinally wrapped in?",
      "answer": "Seaweed.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What element begins with the letter 'K'?",
      "answer": "Krypton",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent has the fewest flowering plants?",
      "answer": "Antarctica.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What railway linked Moscow and Irkutsk in 1900?",
      "answer": "The Trans-Siberian Railway.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Name the world's biggest island.",
      "answer": "Greenland",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Name the world's largest ocean.",
      "answer": "Pacific Ocean.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Name the world's longest river.",
      "answer": "Amazon.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Oprah Winfrey’s production company?",
      "answer": "Harpo.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The acronym NASA stands for what?",
      "answer": "National Aeronautics & Space Administration.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "In ‘The Simpsons’, what is the name of the beer served in Springfield?",
      "answer": "Duff.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Superman works for the Daily Planet, but who works for the Daily Bugle?",
      "answer": "Spiderman, a.k.a. Peter Parker.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What’s the least expensive and most popular fruit?",
      "answer": "Banana.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the last president of the Soviet Union?",
      "answer": "Mikail Gorbachev.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What political system was gradually dismantled in South Africa, starting in 1989?",
      "answer": "Apartheid.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What was developed in the 40s Manhattan Project?",
      "answer": "Atomic Bomb.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Croatia and Slovenia used to be part of which country?",
      "answer": "Yugoslavia.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which caped crusader operated in Gotham city?",
      "answer": "Batman.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which controversial American sportsman had the first names Orenthal James?",
      "answer": "O J Simpson.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Richard starred in Petty Woman?",
      "answer": "Richard Gere.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main airport in Germany?",
      "answer": "Frankfurt.",
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the most famous blonde in Gentlemen Prefer Blondes?",
      "answer": "Marilyn Monroe.",
      "difficulty": 1
    }
  ],

  "2" : [
    {
      "question": "Which is the only American state to begin with the letter ‘p’?",
      "answer": "Pennsylvania.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What’s the largest and densest of the four rocky planets?",
      "answer": "Earth.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which explorer introduced pigs to North America?",
      "answer": "Christopher Columbus.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country has more tractors per capita, Canada, Iceland or Japan?",
      "answer": "Iceland.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which BBC music programme was broadcast weekly between 1964 and 2006?",
      "answer": "Top of the Pops.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What colour is Absynth?",
      "answer": "Green.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "If you had Lafite-Rothschild on your dinner table, what would it be?",
      "answer": "Wine.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "In ex-YU countries, what's the name of the most notorious serial killer?",
      "answer": "Propuh.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What’s the ballet term for a 360-degree turn on one foot?",
      "answer": "Pirouette.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "How is Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta better known in the music industry?",
      "answer": "Lady Gaga.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which planet of our solar system was the first to be discovered by telescope?",
      "answer": "Uranus.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "On a computer keyboard what letter is between Q and E?",
      "answer": "W.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which sitcom about an army hospital in Korea was transmitted in the UK without the canned laughter of the US version?",
      "answer": "M*A*S*H.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Danny starred in Batman Returns?",
      "answer": "Danny De Vito.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which fictional bear thought he had \"very little brain\"?",
      "answer": "Winnie-the-Pooh.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Churchill, Sherman and Panzer were all developed as types of what?",
      "answer": "Tank.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Homer Simpson’s brother?",
      "answer": "Herb Powell.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "There is only one kind of fruit that has its seeds on the outside. Which one?",
      "answer": "Strawberry.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Clark Gable used to do it four or more times a day, but do what?",
      "answer": "Clark Gable used to shower four times a day.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the only rock regularly eaten by humans?",
      "answer": "Salt.",
      "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "In which season do most burglaries take place?",
      "answer": "Winter.",
      "difficulty": 2
    }
  ],

  "3" : [
    {
      "question": "On what day of the week do the most auto accidents happen?",
      "answer": "Saturday.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which mammal has the longest gestation period?",
      "answer": "Elephant.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What national holiday in Mexico has picnickers munching chocolate coffins and sugar skulls?",
      "answer": "The Day of the Dead.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What nation was bounced from the Organisation of American States in 1962?",
      "answer": "Cuba.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who averaged one patent for every three weeks of his life?",
      "answer": "Thomas Edison.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who, after anchoring off Hawaii in 1779, was mistaken for the god Lono? ",
      "answer": "Captain James Cook.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What star sign is \"Gladys Knight\"?",
      "answer": "Gemini.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which writer said, \"Where large sums of money are involved, it is advisable to trust nobody\"?",
      "answer": "Agatha Christie.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Freddie Mercury died in which year?",
      "answer": "1991.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "At the beginning of the 1990s which country had most camels?",
      "answer": "Somalia.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Bono's real name?",
      "answer": "Paul Hewson.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, \"Money is like an arm or a leg, use it or lose it\"?",
      "answer": "Henry Ford.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country had its only gold in men's basketball in the 1980 Olympics?",
      "answer": "Yugoslavia.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The human body has  45 miles of what?",
      "answer": "Nerves.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What does a CAT scan stand for?",
      "answer": "Computerized Axial Topography.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "In digital electronics, what does TTL stand for?",
      "answer": "Transistor Transistor Logic.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Standard TTL circuits operate with a power supply voltage of how much?",
      "answer": "5 Volts.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What 1970s president openly discussed his battle with hemorrhoids?",
      "answer": "Jimmy Carter.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What country did ever-prudent King Farouk I declare war on in 1945?",
      "answer": "Germany.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Slippery Frank Cline was whose bodyguard?",
      "answer": "Al Capone.",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "How old was the man who was granted the first divorce in Irish history?",
      "answer": "68",
      "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "In the 13th century European children were baptized with what?",
      "answer": "Beer.",
      "difficulty": 3
    }
  ]
}